Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. International Advertisements Collection, 1900-2004 and undated, bulk 1965-1990
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Asia/Pacific Series, 1920-2003 and undated (Box AF1)
  - India (Box AP3)
    - Calcutta Office (Box AP4)
      - Phipson and Company (Royal Preserve whiskey), 1985 (Box AP4)
      - Tata Iron and Steel Company Ltd., 1989 (Box AP4)
    - Madras Office (Box AP4)
      - Bombay Dyeing and Manufacturing Company saris, 1985 (Box AP5)
      - Chandamama Publications ( The Heritage magazine), 1984 (Box AP5)
      - Dynavision (Dyanora TV), 1982 (Box AP5)
      - EID Parry (Parrywave) bathrooms, 1985 (with documentation) (Box AP5)
      - General Time Corporation (Westclox), 1982 (Box AP5)
      - New Way chemicals and Polishes (Flush Kleen), 1984 (Box AP5)
      - TT Industries and Textiles (Tantex underwear), 1989 (Box AP5)
      - United India Insurance Company, 1982, 1985 (Box AP5)
    - New Dehli Office (Box AP5)
      - Beecham Group (Horlicks nutritional beverage), 1982 (Box AP5)
      - DCM (Datal 220/Data Logger), 1982 (Box AP5)
      - Escorts Ltd., industrial and commercial machines and equipment, 1984 (Box AP5)
      - Government of India (Box AP5)
        - Department of Tourism, Keep India Beautiful campaign, circa 1989 (Box AP5)
        - Ministry of Welfare, Anti-drug abuse campaign, circa 1980s (Box AP5)
      - Honda Motor Company (Hero Honda motorcycles), 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box AP5)
      - India Today, 1982 (Box AP5)
      - IX Asian Games, 1982 (Box AP5)
      - Maruti Udyog (Maruti 1000 Automobile), 1989-1990 (with documentation) (Box AP5)
      - Modern Bakeries Ltd. (Tingler soft drink), 1984 (Box AP5)
      - National Cancer Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box AP5)
      - [Nestlé: See Oversize Box OV2] (Box AP5)
      - Pepsi (Lehar 7-Up), 1990 (Box AP5)
      - Petroleum Conservation Research Association, 1984 (Box AP5)
    - Multiple Offices (Box AP5)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's (Box AP5)
        - Cold cream/vanishing cream (Bombay Office), 1934 (Box AP5)
        - Pond's talc (Madras Office), 1984 (Box AP5)
      - Welcomegroup (Bombay and New Dehli Offices) (Box AP5)
        - Sea Rock Hotel, 1984, 1988 (Box AP5)
        - Welcomegroup Executive Group, 1989 (Box AP5)
    - Undetermined Office (Box AP5)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1962 (Box AP5)
  - Indonesia (Jakarta Office) (Box AP5)
    - Astra Credit Company, 1990 (Box AP5)
    - Bank Umum National, 1984 (Box AP5)
    - Chiki (Box AP5)
      - Chitato Snacks, 1989 (Box AP5)
      - Jetz Snacks, 1990 (Box AP5)
    - Citicorp (Citibank Visa), 1989-1990 (Box AP5)
    - [Eastman Kodak: See Oversize Box OV2] (Box AP5)
    - Condensfabrick (Sumprima powdered milk), 1988-1989 (Box AP5)
    - Frasier and Neave (F&N sodas), 1984 (Box AP5)
    - IBM, 1988-1990 (Box AP5)
    - Jakarta Post, 1989-1990 (Box AP5)
    - Pasaraya department store, 1989-1990 (Box AP5)
    - Sandoz vitamin C tablets, 1990 (Box AP5)
    - Seiko, 1984 (Box AP5)
    - Sheraton Inn, 1990 (Box AP5)
    - Unilever (Box AP5)
      - Pepsodent toothpaste, 1988-1989 (Box AP5)
      - Sunsilk shampoo, 1988-1990 (Box AP5)
  - Japan (Tokyo Office) (Box AP5)
    - American Drug Corporation, 1988-1989 (See also Oversize Box OV2, Oversize Folder OF3) (Box AP6)
    - Asahi beer, 1984 (See also Oversize Folder OF3) (Box AP6)
    - Bell Atlantic, 1989 (Box AP6)
    - [Burroughs: See Oversize Folder OF3] (Box AP6)
    - [Chiyoda Ear, Nose and Throat Clinic: See Oversize Folder OF3] (Box AP6)
    - Christian Dior perfume, 1982 (Box AP6)
    - Citizen Sjoji, 1989 (Box AP6)
    - Converse sneakers, 1988 (Box AP6)
    - Daniel Diamond Legziel, 1982 (Box AP6)
    - DeBeers Consolidated Mines, 1966, 1982, 1984-1985, 1989-1990 (See also Oversize Box OV2), (2 folders) (Box AP6)
    - Eastman Kodak (Box AP6)
      - Consumer Advertisements, 1971 (Box AP6)
      - Ektachrome, Ektar, 1989-1990 (Box AP6)
      - Kodachrome, 1987-1988 (Box AP6)
      - Kodacolor II, undated (Box AP6)
    - [Ford Motor Company: See Oversize Box OV2] (Box AP6)
    - Hi Liki, beverages, 1984 (Box AP6)
    - Hyatt International Corporation, 1984 (Box AP6)
    - IBM (Box AP6)
      - General services, 1985-1986 (Box AP6)
      - JX Computer, 1985 (Box AP6)
    - International Wool Secretariat, 1964, 1971, 1980 (See also Oversize Box OV2) (Box AP6)
    - [Jaguar: See Oversize Box OV2] (Box AP6)
    - Kuipo, 1989 (Box AP6)
    - [Marubeni Corporation: See Oversize Box OV2] (Box AP6)
    - Parker Pen Company, circa 1969 (Box AP6)
    - PepsiCo: (See also Oversize Folder OF3 (Box AP6)
    - R.J. Reynolds (See also Oversize Box OV2) (Box AP6)
      - Salem, 1988-1989 (Box AP6)
      - Vantage, 1989 (Box AP6)
      - Winston, 1988 (Box AP6)
      - Yves Saint Laurent, cigarettes, 1988-1989 (Box AP6)
    - Rolex, 1968, 1986 (See also Oversize Box OV2) (Box AP6)
    - [Rowntree Mackintosh: See Oversize Box OV2] (Box AP6)
    - [Rustenberg Platinum Mines: See Oversize Box OV2] (Box AP6)
    - Suchiro Shuzu, 1989 (See also Oversize Box OV2, Oversize Folder OF3) (Box AP6)
    - Trafalgar, 1989 (Box AP6)
    - Unilever (Nippon-Lever; Timotei hair care products), 1987 (Box AP6)
    - [Unkai Shuzo: moved to Oversize Materials, Box OV2] (Box AP6)
    - Warner-Lambert (See also Oversize Box OV2) (Box AP6)
      - Ena candy, 1988-1989 (Box AP6)
      - Jordan toothbrushes, 1987-1988 (Box AP6)
      - Listerine, 1988-1989 (Box AP6)
      - Winds chewing gum, 1988-1989 (Box AP6)
    - Wedgewood china, circa 1984-1985 (Box AP6)
  - Korea (Seoul Office) (Box AP6)
    - [Ford Motor Company: See Oversize Box OV2] (Box AP6)
  - Lebanon (Beirut Office) (Box AP6)
    - Eastman Kodak - trade, 1966 (Box AP7)
  - Malaysia (Kuala Lumpur Office) (Box AP7)
    - Findus, lemon cream pie, 1980s (Box AP7)
    - Funland, cream crackers, 1980s (Box AP7)
    - IBM, 1985-1987 (See also Oversize Box OV2) (Box AP7)
      - 25th Anniversary campaign (Box AP7)
      - Personal computer (Box AP7)
      - Planet Earth (television series) (Box AP7)
    - Kellogg's Cornflakes, 1980s (Box AP7)
    - Kraft (Cheese products, Tang) circa 1980s-1998 (Box AP7)
    - Lux (advertisement in Mandarin), circa 1980s (Box AP7)
    - Malaysian Airline System, 1976, 1984 (Box AP7)
    - Malaysian Banking Berhad (Box AP7)
      - Banking services, 1981 (Box AP7)
      - Visa Card, 1982 (Box AP7)
    - Malaysian National Insurance, 1984 (Box AP7)
    - Metrojaya department store, 1984, 1988, 1990 (Box AP7)
    - Nestlé (Box AP7)
      - Maggi noodles, 1980s (Box AP7)
      - Maval malted drink, 1983 (Box AP7)
      - Various chocolates, 1980s (Box AP7)
    - R.J. Reynolds (See also Oversize Box OV2, Oversize Folder OF4) (Box AP7)
      - Salem, 1982, 1984 (Box AP7)
      - Winston, 1984-1985 (Box AP7)
    - Tourist and Development Corporation, 1981 (Box AP7)
    - Unilever (Box AP7)
      - Breece detergent, 1981 (Box AP7)
      - Close-Up toothpaste, 1973 (Box AP7)
      - Lux soap, 1985 (Box AP7)
  - [New Zealand: See Box AP10] (Box AP7)
  - Philippines (Manila Office) (Box AP7)
    - Araneta Center, circa 1980s (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP7)
    - Carlsberg, 1984 (Box AP7)
    - Central Bank of the Philippines, 1984 (Box AP7)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1938, 1962-1963, (2 folders) (Box AP7)
    - [Citibank: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
    - CPC International (Knorr chicken cubes), 1987 (Box AP7)
    - Eastman Kodak (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP7)
      - Consumer advertisements, 1971 (Box AP7)
      - Developing services, 1987-1988 (Box AP7)
      - Eastman color-intermediate film, 1988 (Box AP7)
      - S-Series camera, 1990 (Box AP7)
      - SEA Games (Jakarta 1987), 1985 (Box AP7)
    - Ford Motor Company (Granada), 1981 (Box AP7)
    - IBM Personal Computer, 1985 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP7)
    - Jourdan et Cie, fashions, 1981, 1984, 1987 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP7)
    - Kraft (Dart and Kraft; Cheese Whiz), 1987-2003 (See also Oversize Folder OF4) (Box AP7)
    - [Land Bank of the Philippines: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
    - National Panasonic (Matsushita) batteries, 1988 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP7)
    - [PepsiCo: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
    - [Philips: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
    - Publishers Association of the Philippines reading campaign, 1981 (Box AP7)
    - [Pure Foods: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
    - [Royal Dutch Petroleum: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
    - Rubberworld Inc. (Mighty Kid) footwear, 1987 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP7)
    - S.C. Johnson and Son (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP7)
      - Off! mosquito repellant, 1988 (Box AP7)
      - Pledge, furniture wax, 1985 (Box AP7)
      - Raid, insecticide spray, 1987 (Box AP7)
      - Virex, disinfectants, 1987-1988 (Box AP7)
    - Scott Paper Company (Box AP7)
      - Scottissue toilet paper, 1981, 1987 (Box AP7)
      - Soft 'n' Pretty tissues, 1981 (Box AP7)
    - [Unilever: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
    - [Warner-Lambert: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
  - Singapore Office (Box AP7)
    - [ABN Bank: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
    - BTW Car Rentals, 1981 (Box AP7)
    - [Citicorp: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
    - Eastman Kodak developing services, 1987 (Box AP7)
    - [Fraser & Neave: See Oversize Box OV3, Oversize Folder OF5] (Box AP7)
    - Holiday Inn, 1990 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP7)
    - Hyatt International Corporation, 1987 (Box AP7)
    - [IBM: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
    - Kellogg Sunglow, orange drink, 1980 (Box AP7)
    - [Metro Group: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
    - Ministry of Defense (Singapore Armed Forces), 1984 (Box AP7)
    - Nestlé (Box AP7)
      - After Eight chocolate mints, 1991 (Box AP7)
      - Kit Kat, 1997 (Box AP7)
      - Polo peppermints, 1990 (Box AP7)
    - Richard Ellis Property Consultants, 1984 (Box AP7)
    - S.C. Johnson and Son, 1984 (Box AP7)
      - Off! insect repellant (Box AP7)
      - Toilet Duck cleanser (Box AP7)
    - Times Publishing ( Singapore Business), 1987-1990 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP7)
    - Tokyu Group (Claymore Condominiums), 1985 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP7)
    - Toyota (Carina), 1981 (Box AP7)
    - Wearne Brothers Jaguar (Malayan Motors), undated (Box AP7)
  - Sri Lanka (Colombo Office) (Box AP7)
    - Mackwoods and Winthrop (Panadol), 1985 (Box AP7)
    - Nestlé (Nestomalt nutritional beverage), 1985 (Box AP7)
    - [Unilever: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP7)
  - Taiwan (Box AP7)
    - Taipei Office (Box AP7)
      - E-57, 1989 (Box AP8)
      - [Citicorp: See Oversize Folder OF6] (Box AP8)
      - Eastman Kodak (Kodacolor film), 1989 (Box AP8)
      - Ford (Festiva and Telstar), 1989 (Box AP8)
      - IBM, 1988-1989 (Box AP8)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1990 (Box AP8)
      - National Investment Trust Company, 1989 (Box AP8)
      - R.J. Reynolds (Yves Saint Laurent cigarettes), 1988 (Box AP8)
    - Undetermined Office (Box AP8)
      - Citicorp (Citibank Visa and Diner's Club credit cards), 1989, (3 folders) (Box AP8)
      - Nike, 1996 (Box AP8)
  - Thailand (Bangkok Office) (Box AP8)
    - Camus International, cognac, 1989 (Box AP9)
    - Diethelm (Ocean Pacific clothes), 1990 (Box AP9)
    - Eastman Kodak (Kodacolor film), 1989 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP9)
    - Holiday Inn, 1990 (Box AP9)
    - Hyatt Hotels, 1985 (Box AP9)
    - IBM, 1987, 1990 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP9)
    - Kraft cheese products, 1989-2003, (2 folders) (Box AP9)
    - Mac Company Ltd. (McJean), 1989 (Box AP9)
    - Mitsubishi Corporation home electronics, 1990 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP9)
    - Motorola, pagers, 1997 (Box AP9)
    - Nike, 1997 (Box AP9)
    - Post Publishing ( The Bangkok Post), 1989 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP9)
    - President Park, 1989 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP9)
    - Regal International Hotels, 1987 (Box AP9)
    - Royal Dutch Petroleum Company (Molla motor oil), 1990 (Box AP9)
    - S.C. Johnson and Son (Glade air freshener), 1989-1990 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP9)
    - Scott Paper Company (Lady Scott) paper products, 1990 (Box AP9)
    - Siam Cement Group, 1987 (Box AP9)
    - [Singer Company: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP9)
    - Standard Enterprise feminine hygiene products (Box AP9)
      - Pub Pak, 1989 (Box AP9)
      - Sanita, 1987 (Box AP9)
    - Thai Farmers Bank, banking and credit card services, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box AP9)
    - Thai Theparog (Golden Mountain soy sauce), 1990 (Box AP9)
    - T.N. Engineering (NEC) telephones and fax machines, 1985 (Box AP9)
    - Unifab Equipment Company (Uni-Aire air conditioners), 1989 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP9)
    - [Warner-Lambert (Listerine): See Oversize Folder OF7] (Box AP9)
  - United Arab Emirates (Dubai Office) (Box AP9)
    - [J. Walter Thompson Company: See Oversize Folder OF8] (Box AP9)
  - Australia (Box AP9)
    - Melbourne Office (Box AP9)
      - Coats Patons (Box AP10)
        - Bonds women's and childrens underwear, 1982, 1984, 1989-1990 (Box AP10)
        - Dri-Glo towels, circa 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Patons fashions, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Sirdar knits, 1988 (Box AP10)
        - Sunioafa towels, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Taeger menswear, 1984 (Box AP10)
      - Dynomax, 1997 (Box AP10)
      - Eastman Kodak (Kodacolor VR film and paper), 1984 (Box AP10)
      - Electrolux (Flymo XE 38 lawnmower), 1984 (Box AP10)
      - Ford Motor Company (Box AP10)
        - Fairlane, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Falcon, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Festiva, circa 1996 (Box AP10)
        - Spectron, 1984 (Box AP10)
      - Herald Sun, 1995 (Box AP10)
      - Interwest Hotels, 1988 (Box AP10)
      - Kraft (Box AP10)
        - Cheestik, 1996 (Box AP10)
        - Coon cheese, 1985 (Box AP10)
        - Cracker Barrel cheese spread, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Dip 'n' Spread, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Light 'n' Lively, 1982-1985 (Box AP10)
        - Miracle Whip, 1978, 1980 (Box AP10)
        - Philadelphia cream cheese, 1983-1984 (Box AP10)
        - Salad dressing, 1985 (Box AP10)
        - Shredded cheese, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Singles, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Various cheese products, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Weight Watchers cheese, 1984 (Box AP10)
      - National Australia Bank, 1982-1984 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP10)
      - Nylex (Box AP10)
        - Contact brand contact paper, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Micromagic microwave cookware, 1984 (Box AP10)
      - Scott Paper Company (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP10)
        - Libra panty liners, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Libra Fleur tampons, 1988 (Box AP10)
      - Stolichnaya vodka, circa 2000 (Box AP10)
    - Sydney Office (Box AP10)
      - [Australian Writers and Directors Association: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP10)
      - British and American Tobacco (Benson & Hedges), 1982, 1987-1988 (Box AP10)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's cold and vanishing cream, 1931 (Box AP10)
      - DeBeers, circa 1980, 1989 (Box AP10)
      - Douwe Egberts (Drum tobacco), 1984 (Box AP10)
      - Dunlop Holidays Ltd. (Box AP10)
        - Dunlop golf balls, 1981 (Box AP10)
        - Slazenger sports equipment, 1982 (Box AP10)
      - ICL computers, 1982-1983 (Box AP10)
      - Jantzen swimsuits, 1933 (Box AP10)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, Christmas-related materials, 1988 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP10)
      - Kellogg Company (Box AP10)
        - Health campaign, 1988 (Box AP10)
        - Nutri-Grain, 1988 (Box AP10)
        - Rice Bubbles, 1960, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Unidentifiable advertisement, 1982 (Box AP10)
      - Kelvinator appliances, undated (Box AP10)
      - Nestlé (Papa Giuseppi frozen foods), 1982 (Box AP10)
      - Reckitt and Colman Ltd. (Orlando wines), 1982, 1984 (Box AP10)
      - Schroder Darling and Company investment banking, 1984 (Box AP10)
      - The Smith Family (charity), 1988 (Box AP10)
      - Unilever (Box AP10)
        - Harmony hair color, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Lan Choo tea (Bushell's), undated (Box AP10)
        - Lux soap, 1985 (Box AP10)
        - Sunsilk hair care products, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Timotei shampoo, circa 1980s (Box AP10)
      - Union Carbide (Eveready batteries), 1982 (Box AP10)
      - Wittingdon Investments (Weston's biscuits), 1988 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP10)
    - Undetermined Office (Box AP10)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1962 (Box AP10)
      - Kraft (Jacobs, Philadelphia cream cheese), 1998 (Box AP10)
      - Volta vacuum cleaners, 1984 (Box AP10)
  - New Zealand (Box AP10)
    - Auckland Office (Box AP10)
      - Eastman Kodak (Box AP10)
        - Corporate advertisement, 1990 (Box AP10)
        - Ektar film, 1990 (Box AP10)
        - EXR motion picture film, 1990 (Box AP10)
      - [New Zealand Cooperative Pig Market Association: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP10)
    - Wellington Office (Box AP10)
      - ANZ Banking Group (See also Oversize Folder OF9) (Box AP10)
        - Banking services, circa 1988 (Box AP10)
        - Master Card, 1984 (Box AP10)
      - Brooklyn Bakeries (Sunshine bread), 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP10)
      - IBM, 1988 (See also Oversize Box OV3) (Box AP10)
      - ICI New Zealand (Subsidiary of ICI Australia) suncare products, 1984, 1988 (Box AP10)
      - [Inland Revenue Department: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP10)
      - Municipal Electricity Department, 1988 (Box AP10)
      - Nabisco Brands (Griffin & Son) candy, 1987 (Box AP10)
      - New Zealand Water Safety Council, 1984 (Box AP10)
      - Rhone-Poulene S.A. (May & Baker N.Z. Ltd.) Treflan brand agrochemicals, 1984, 1987 (Box AP10)
      - Unilever (Box AP10)
        - Lux liquid dish soap, 1984 (Box AP10)
        - Omo laundry detergent, 1988 (Box AP10)
    - Undetermined Office (Box AP10)
      - [Breadmill: See Oversize Box OV3] (Box AP10)
      - Club Med, 1984 (Box AP10)
        [Produced with JWT Hong Kong]
- Canada Series, 1921-1997 and undated (Box AP10)
  Arranged alphabetically by office name and product.
  - Montreal Office (Box AP10)
    - Abbott Laboratories (Box CA1)
      - Consumer magazine, 1972-1979 (Box CA1)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1971-1972 (Box CA1)
      - Trade magazine, 1971-1979 (Box CA1)
    - ALCAN Aluminum Limited (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA1)
      - Consumer magazine, 1960-1963, 1989-1990 (Box CA1)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1958 (Box CA1)
      - Trade newspaper, 1962-1966 (Box CA1)
    - Allegheny Airlines (Box CA1)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1977-1978 (Box CA1)
      - Trade magazine, 1976-1977 (Box CA1)
    - Allied Chemical (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA1)
      - Consumer magazine, 1963-1965 (Box CA1)
      - Consumer magazine (Barrett Products), 1940-1963, (1-7 of 12 folders) (Box CA1)
      - Consumer newspaper (Barrett Products), 1940-1963 (continued), (8-12 of 12 folders) (Box CA2)
      - Trade magazine, 1959-1965, (6 folders) (Box CA2)
      - Trade magazine (Barrett Products), 1940-1961, (1-7 of 17 folders) (Box CA2)
      - Trade magazine (Barrett Products), 1940-1961 (continued), (8-17 of 17 folders) (Box CA3)
      - Trade newspaper, 1960-1965 (Box CA3)
      - Trade newspaper (Barrett Products), 1943-1947, 1951, (2 folders) (Box CA3)
    - Aquascatum of London (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA4)
      - Consumer magazine, 1956-1968, (4 folders) (Box CA4)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1955-1968, (4 folders) (Box CA4)
    - Atlific Inns, consumer newspaper, 1974-1975 (Box CA4)
    - AVCO, consumer magazine, 1969-1970 (Box CA4)
    - Avis Rent-a-Car (Box CA4)
      - Consumer magazine, 1959-1963, (2 folders) (Box CA4)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1957-1963 (Box CA4)
    - Blue Water Seafoods (Box CA4)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1956-1962 (Box CA4)
      - Trade magazine, 1956-1960 (Box CA4)
      - Trade newspaper, 1957-1958 (Box CA4)
    - Brillo Manufacturing Company (Box CA4)
      - Consumer magazine, 1956-1957 (Box CA4)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1956-1959 (Box CA4)
      - Trade magazine, 1958 (Box CA4)
    - Brooke Bond foods (Box CA5)
      - Consumer magazine, 1970-1980, (2 folders) (Box CA5)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1970-1979 (Box CA5)
      - Trade magazine, 1970-1978 (Box CA5)
    - Burroughs Wellcome and Company (Box CA5)
      - Trade magazine, 1972 (Box CA5)
      - Trade newspaper, 1972 (Box CA5)
    - Calvert (Box CA5)
      - Consumer magazine, 1968-1971 (Box CA5)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1968-1971, (3 folders) (Box CA5)
      - Trade magazine, 1969-1970 (Box CA5)
    - Canada Advertising Advisory Board, 1978 (Box CA5)
    - Canada Mink Breeders (Box CA5)
      - Consumer magazine, 1960-1964, 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box CA5)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1960-1964 (Box CA5)
      - Trade magazine, 1960-1963 (Box CA5)
      - Trade newspaper, 1960-1964 (Box CA5)
    - Canadair (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA5)
      - Consumer magazine, 1989-1990 (Box CA5)
      - Trade magazine, 1989 (Box CA5)
    - Canadelle, consumer newspaper, 1979 (Box CA5)
    - Canadian Distilleries (Box CA5)
      - Consumer magazine, 1972 (Box CA5)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1972 (Box CA5)
    - Canadian Salt Company (Box CA5)
      - Consumer magazine, 1943-1964, (3 folders) (Box CA5)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1943-1957 (Box CA6)
      - Trade magazine, 1940-1960, (4 folders) (Box CA6)
      - Trade newspaper, 1940-1961 (Box CA6)
      - Trade poster designs, 1954-1957 (Box CA6)
    - Ciba, consumer newspaper, 1957 (Box CA6)
    - Concordia Estates (Box CA6)
      - Trade magazine, 1964-1965 (Box CA6)
      - Trade newspaper, 1964-1965 (Box CA6)
    - Congoleum, trade magazine, 1976 (Box CA6)
    - Consumers Distributing, consumer newspaper, 1971-1972 (Box CA6)
    - Cordon Bleu (Box CA6)
      - Consumer magazine, 1977-1979 (Box CA6)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1977-1979 (Box CA6)
    - Dominion Dairies (Box CA6)
      - Consumer magazine, 1977-1979 (Box CA6)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1977-1979 (Box CA6)
    - Dominion Glass Company (Box CA6)
      - Consumer magazine 1951-1952 (Box CA6)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1949-1954 (Box CA6)
      - Trade magazine, 1953-1965 (Box CA6)
    - Eastman Chemical Inter-American (Box CA6)
      - Consumer magazine, 1972 (Box CA6)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1969-1971 (Box CA6)
    - Edith Serai, consumer newspaper, 1970 (Box CA7)
    - Enterprise Advertising Associates, trade magazine, 1984 (Box CA7)
    - Federal Express, consumer magazine, 1990 (Box CA7)
    - Fisher Brothers Incorporated, consumer newspaper, 1970 (Box CA7)
    - Fisheries Council of Canada, trade magazine, 1956-1961 (Box CA7)
    - Ford Motor Company (Box CA7)
      - Consumer magazine, 1958 (Box CA7)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1958 (Box CA7)
    - Forest Engineering Research Institute of Canada, consumer newspaper, 1979 (Box CA7)
    - Frank W. Horner, consumer newspaper, 1961 (Box CA7)
    - [Grand Themes: See Oversize Box OV4] (Box CA7)
    - [Greb Industries: See Oversize Folder OF10] (Box CA7)
    - Hattori Trading Company, consumer newspaper, 1964 (Box CA7)
    - Hoffman-LaRoche, trade magazine, 1958 (Box CA7)
    - Hygrade Food products, consumer newspaper, 1958-1959 (Box CA7)
    - Irving Oil Company, consumer newspaper, 1966 (Box CA7)
    - J. Walter Thompson (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA7)
      - Consumer magazine, 1957-1964 (Box CA7)
      - Consumer newspaper, 1957-1975 (Box CA7)
    - Jantzen, consumer magazine, 1968-1973 (Box CA7)
    - Johnson & Johnson, trade magazine, 1975 (Box CA7)
    - Kawasaki, consumer magazine, 1977 (Box CA7)
    - Kraft (See also Oversize Box OV4) (Box CA8)
      - Individual products (Box CA8)
        - Canadian Slices, 1949-1985, (7 folders) (Box CA8)
        - Miracle Whip, 1940-1990, (8 folders) (Box CA8)
        - Velveeta, 1941-1985, (6 folders) (Box CA8)
      - Miscellaneous and multiple products (Box CA9)
        - Consumer magazine, 1940-1975, (18 folders) (Box CA9)